https://unitedfoodbank.org/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy – United Food Bank
Skip to contentMedia Center|Agency Resources
FacebookTwitterInstagramYouTubeDonate TodayUnited Food BankNourishing Arizona Communities Give HelpVolunteer NowHost a Food DriveBecome a FundraiserMobile Volunteer EventsCorporate SponsorshipsCurrent Food Drives & FundraisersGet HelpFind FoodUnited Food Bank Food DistributionsResources for YouPartner AgenciesAbout UsMedia CenterHistoryBoard of DirectorsStaffFinancialsAgency ResourcesJob OpportunitiesStories & MediaMedia CenterIn the NewsThe FEED BlogShare Your StoryAll PostsContact Give HelpVolunteer NowHost a Food DriveBecome a FundraiserMobile Volunteer EventsCorporate SponsorshipsCurrent Food Drives & FundraisersGet HelpFind FoodUnited Food Bank Food DistributionsResources for YouPartner AgenciesAbout UsMedia CenterHistoryBoard of DirectorsStaffFinancialsAgency ResourcesJob OpportunitiesStories & MediaMedia CenterIn the NewsThe FEED BlogShare Your StoryAll PostsContactYou are here:HomeAbout UsPrivacy PolicyPrivacy Policy United Food Bank (hereinafter “UFB”) hereby acknowledges and ascribes to the Association of Fundraising Professionals “Donor Bill of Rights” and declares its commitment to protect the privacy and confidentiality of individuals who browse or engage in any activity on this website. You are here:HomeAbout UsPrivacy PolicyPRIVACY POLICYUNITED FOOD BANKPRIVACY POLICYEffective October 30, 2015Our Commitment to PrivacyUnited Food Bank (hereinafter “UFB”) hereby acknowledges and ascribes to the Association of Fundraising Professionals “Donor Bill of Rights” and declares its commitment to protect the privacy and confidentiality of individuals who browse or engage in any activity on this website.The following Privacy Policy applies to any and all information provided to and received by UFB, both online and offline, on any Platform, (“Platform” includes UFB’s website, mobile apps, and social media), as well as to any electronic, written, or oral communications.  This Privacy Policy applies to any and all information that may be provided directly to UFB or indirectly to Third-Party Service Providers and Advertising Partners (hereinafter “Partners”) on and through this website. This Privacy Policy will also define the type and scope of any and all information collected and submitted through this website.UFB does not rent, sell, or exchange donor information with any third-party.The Information We CollectOn this website, individuals may make financial contributions, order products, request information, search or register to receive materials and will be asked to voluntarily provide Personal Information which may include: Name, Mailing Address, Email Address, Telephone Number, Credit Card/Debit Card Information, Non-Personal Information and Other Information required to acknowledge tribute gifts, request information, volunteer services, or to register and sign-up for events and other activities.DefinitionsPersonal Information:  “Personal Information” is hereby defined as any information that identifies or could be used to specifically identify a natural person.  Personal Information does not include information about corporate entities or information that is encoded, aggregated or anonymized, or that may already reside in the public domain.Non-Personal Information: “Non-Personal Information” is hereby defined as any technical information that cannot be used to specifically identify a natural person which is automatically collected upon access or use of this website.  Non-Personal Information may include:  IP Address, ISP, Browser, Operating System, Digital Device, and Language; Referring Page, Exit Page, and URL; Date, Time, Browsing History, Clicks, and Search Terms; Cookies1, JavaScript Tags, Web Beacons, Clear-Gifs, Pixel-Tags, Flash Cookies, and other objects.  Pixel tags enable UFB and its Partners to learn what brings browsers to this website.Other Information:  “Other Information” is hereby defined as Browsing Activity.  Browsing Activity may be shared with UFB Partners for the purpose of analyzing, managing, reporting, tailoring, and optimizing advertising that may appear on this website and elsewhere.Do Not Track (“DNT”).  “Do Not Track” is a technology that enables users to opt out of tracking by websites they do not visit, including analytic services, advertising networks, and social platforms. DNT signals a user’s opt-out-preference with an HTTP header, a simple technology that is completely compatible with existing web applications.  UFB assumes no responsibility for responding to DNT web-browser signals.1 “Cookies” are small packets of digital-data stored on digital devices which “remember” information about web-browsing history.  “Session Cookies” expire once a web-browser is closed.  “Persistent Cookies” remain on digital devices until they are deleted.  UFB employs Java scripting to record and trigger a sequence of events which optimize a user’s experience on this website.  Individuals may elect to disable “Cookies” on their digital devices; however, this may affect the functionality of this website.  Consult your web-browser’s documentation to learn how to disable “Cookies”.Advertising PartnersUFB may enter into agreements with Partners to deliver relevant, user-targeted, non-intrusive advertising.  Partners will not be granted access to Personal Information; however, UFB may grant access to Non-Personal Information with Partners.  Partners maintain their own privacy policies which should be reviewed in connection with the use of this website.Significant partners currently include, but are not limited to:Google Analytics.  “Google Analytics” is a web service provided by Google, Inc. (“Google”).  Google places “Cookies” on digital devices to track internet usage and browsing history.  Non-Personal Information gathered by “Cookies” is transmitted and stored on Google servers in the United States.  Google collects information anonymously and aggregates this data to report on website activity, internet usage and trends.  Google may deliver this information to third-parties where required to do so by law or where such third-parties process information on Google’s behalf.By using UFB’s website, you expressly consent to the processing and sharing of Non-Personal Information by Google in the manner and for the purposes stated above.   Individuals may opt-out of Google Analytics on their digital devices without affecting navigation of this website.  Consult Google and/or your browser’s documentation for information on how to do this.How We Use and Share the Information    UFB uses Personal, Non-Personal and Other Information to process donations, solicit feedback, and acquire information; to disseminate information about UFB activities, programs, services and to connect people to resources.  UFB may employ other Partners to perform various functions to provide technical support and customer service.  UFB may grant Partners access to Personal, Non-Personal, and Other Information required to perform such functions to the extent permitted by law:  (i) when required by law, court order, or other government or law enforcement authority or regulatory body; or (ii) whenever UFB believes that disclosing such information is necessary or advisable to protect the rights, property, or safety of UFB and others.  In an ongoing effort to better understand website usage, UFB may also aggregate and share information with Partners to improve, enhance, manage, and maintain this website and social media platforms.   This aggregate data does not identify individuals personally and may be shared with Partners to perform various functions for contracted services to the extent allowed by law.Accessing and Modifying Information and Communication PreferencesUpon request, UFB may grant access to Personal Information that we and our Partners maintain.   Individuals may review and/or make changes to their Personal Information by contacting UFB.  In addition, individuals may also manage receipt of communications from UFB by clicking the “Unsubscribe” link located on the bottom of UFB marketing e-mails or by requesting the same through this website.  UFB will employ every commercially reasonable step to process such requests in a timely manner.  However, it may not be possible to modify or completely remove information from our subscription databases in all circumstances.How We Protect the InformationWhile UFB will employ every commercially reasonable step to protect Personal Information that is entered, stored, and transmitted by this website against loss, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and destruction, no security system is impenetrable.  UFB cannot guarantee the security of Personal Information from cyber-attack or interception on the Internet.  Information sent or received via E-mail from this website may not be secure and special care should be taken when deciding what information to send via E-mail.Important Notices to Non-U.S. ResidentsIt is important to note that this website and servers are operated in the United States.  If you are located outside of the United States, please be aware that any Personal Information provided to us will be transferred to the United States.  You hereby and unconditionally consent to the transfer of such Personal Information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.   For questions regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact UFB as described in the “How to Contact Us” section below.  We will investigate your question, respond to your inquiry, and attempt to address your privacy concerns.External WebsitesUFB’s website contains links to Partners and third-party websites.  UFB does not administer the privacy policies of such websites and is not responsible for the content and privacy policies of these websites.  Always review the privacy policy and terms of use when visiting other websites.ChildrenUFB does not knowingly collect Personal Information from children under the age of thirteen (13) on this website.  If you are under the age of thirteen, please do not provide your Personal Information.  We encourage parents and legal guardians to monitor children’s Internet usage to help enforce this provision of this Privacy Policy. Please instruct children never to disclose Personal Information over the Internet without permission.  If you have reason to believe a child under the age of thirteen has disclosed Personal Information on this website, please contact us, and we will endeavor to delete said information from our databases.Acceptance of Terms & Changes to this Privacy PolicyBy visiting UFB website, you agree to be bound by the terms of this Privacy Policy.  Capitalized terms not specifically defined in this Privacy Policy shall have the meaning set forth in our Terms of Use.  This Privacy Policy is effective as of Friday, October 30, 2015.  UFB may change this Privacy Policy from time to time.  Please be aware that, to the extent permitted by law, use of Personal Information and Other Information is governed by the Privacy Policy in effect at the time we collect the information.  Please refer back to this Privacy Policy on a regular basis.How to Contact UsIf you have questions about this Privacy Policy, or wish to opt out and no longer receive direct mail, e-mail, electronic or social media communications, please contact United Food Bank via: E-mail at donations@unitedfoodbank.org and place “PRIVACY POLICY” in the subject line of this e-mail; or by mailing a letter to Privacy Administrator, United Food Bank, 245 S. Nina Drive, Mesa Arizona 85210; or by calling United Food bank at (480) 926-4897, ext. 233.– See more at: https://unitedfoodbank.org/privacy-policy/#sthash.e3GTwdPC.dpuf
United Food Bank245 S. Nina Drive Mesa, AZ 85210 Phone: (480) 926-4897
Volunteer Center 358 E. Javelina Ave. Mesa, AZ 85210 (Closed most holidays)
United Food Bank is an equal opportunity provider.DonateEvery $1 donated can help provide 5 nutritious meals to feed hungry children, seniors and families in Arizona.DONATE NOWUnited Food Bank is a Qualifying Charitable Organization (QCO) and donations are eligible for the Arizona State Charitable Tax Credit QCO code: #20206United Food Bank is a 501(c)3 Organization – Tax ID: 86-0505273
Find FoodHelp Yourself Purchase CooperativePartner AgenciesResources for YouNondiscrimination StatementAdvocacyBoard of DirectorsStaffFinancialsJob OpportunitiesPrivacy PolicyAgency ResourcesCopyright 2020 © United Food BankDonateVolunteerGet HelpNews & EventsContactServices Go to Top
